

ABOUT ME

I'm a game programmer specializing in **object-oriented programming**, with almost 3 years of experience in the industry.

I have worked at Melbot, where I was involved in game development and publishing for consoles, as well as handling their ports.

Additionally, I have gained experience working for Magnetic, where I focused on mobile game development for a **live game**.

Furthermore, I successfully launched my own Android game, completed several internships and work as a Unity teacher for Xnergic.

I'm a very enterprising person, outgoing and eager for new experiences.

COMPETENCES

Languages

- C#
- C++
- Lua
- Python

Engines

- Unity
- Unreal
- Offica
- Defold

CONTACT

- +34 636-98-24-40
- Portfolio Personal web
- LinkedIn

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (Native)
- Catalan (Native)
- English (Advanced)

MARINA CHAVARRIA

GAME PROGRAMMER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Console Game Programmer - Melbot

January 2022-April 2023 October 2023 - Current

Nick Jr Party Adventure - PC & Console

- Implement key gameplay systems. (level, menus, rewards...)
- Re-develop a new UI system with DoTween, for improved performance.
- Develop the PlayStation 5 port and supported the PlayStation 4 port.
- Optimizing the game for Switch due to its limitations.
- Developed a tool for creating levels that was highly flexible, allowing designers and artists to seamlessly incorporate their artwork into the tool, with the map adapting to the art.
- Working with the Nintendo SDK, PS5 and PS4.

My Little Pony - PC & Console

- · Develop gameplay features.
- Responsible for the port Play Station 5 port.
- Enhance its performance and resolve existing bugs.
- Working with the Nintendo SDK and Xbox to assist in the development.

Mobile Game Programmer - Magnetic

April 2023 - October 2023

Art Heist Puzzle - Android and IOS

- Developed significant features for a live game.
- Implementation of code for the client-server communication.
- · Actively applied dependency injection in the codebase.
- Integrated third-party libraries and SDKinto existing project.
- Debugged complex problems in existing code base.
- Develop the first in-game purchase system, from the client side.
- Participated in design meetings with other team members to discuss ideas for future content.

Game Programmer Intern - Kaneda Games

June 2021-August 2021

- My team and I, develop a local multiplayer jet ski game. I was in charge of organizing the game loop structure and the UI system.
- Unity teacher Xnergic Tecnocampus

October 2020 - January 2022

 Provide classes about Unity, Scratch, and Arduino to children throughout the year.

EDUCATION

Videogame Programming and Design

2018 - 2023

Tecnocampus Pompeu Fabra

SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptability
- Attention to detailTime managment
- Communcation
- Problem-Solving
- Teamwork